So over here, as you see, we can see the chat history of us.
So for example, my top 20 French phrases, right?
So this is the conversation we had.
We also have logo research request.
And by clicking on these three dots of each item,
we will be able to share this very conversation.
We'll be able to start a group chat
so we can add other friends of us
and start having a group in chat GPT.
We can rename our chat.
So I can say not logo research request,
but let's say the takeoff college deep research, right?
I can also archive or delete a chat.
So when we archive a chat, it is renewable, right?
So we can take it back, bring it back.
But when we delete it, it's gone forever, you know?
And that's all that we have.
We can also come to a library over here.
So you saw the new chat.
New chat is for starting off new conversations.
By coming to library, we'll be able to see the media
that is generated by chat GPT.
And for example, we're able to see the new logo
that GPT just generated for us.
And it's listed over here as well.
And we'll be able to see all of them images over here
in the library tab.
We also have projects.
We don't have anything to do with this for now.
And go up on our again trip.
Yeah, these are projects.
So project is something bigger than a chat.
So a project can contain a couple of chats, you know?
As you see, projects keep chats, files,
and custom instructions in one place.
Yep.
And we're also able to search these chats
when there's a lot of them using this option.